UX
Styling need completing here...
Pick a colour scheme and go with it. Once done 
Voting down on an article actually votes up… ✓
I can’t see the rest of the comments. They just run of the bottom of the page. :(
What does the user link do?
Usernames need to start as actual values or tell the user who to login as. They won’t know what valid usernames are. ✓
Errors need to be displayed if an invalid username is entered. ✓
NC news banner should be a link back to the homepage. ✓
Tabs component will have to be moved on mobile view. Other components should be fine however.
Sorting is great but the buttons stay checked when you press them.
Can I vote on comments as well please? ✓
Footer should say something other than footer.
Change the title and favicon from the basic react app.
Posting articles works in an interesting way…. ✓
Need a visual confirmation of posting an article. Navigate to that article? ✓
Posting doesn’t work on an individual topic page. ? ✓
Posting comments works but should be added to the list optimistically.
Am I allowed to post without being logged in?
Console.loooooooogs…….. Clear em out :D
Can i delete things?

Code
Readme needs writing. Make sure you include links to both the live version and the back-end.
Is this deployed? Make sure the redirects work if it is.
Reach router is not a dependency, add it to the package.json. ✓
Remove the .env file, package.lock.json and eslint from your package.json. Your rules will still work but react-scripts requires a specific version that you have overwritten. This will stop the preflight error. ✓
Don’t call session storage in the state directly. Use the appropriate lifecycle methods. ✓
Remove any files you are not using.
You need to put inc_votes into an object in the api call to fix the voting bug. ✓
You have setup your style folder and then not used it. Put all the css in here. :D 
User and sidebar components have not yet been implemented.
Deleting an article doesn’t re-render anything.
Error handling is conspicuously missing.
Methods in Single Article shouldn’t have capitals. ✓
Articles and ArticlesByTopic are extremely similar. If the only thing that’s going to change is the api call just check the props and decide it there. ROUTES?
Pagination needs adding to get the rest of your articles.

Pagination
User page
Errors
Sidebar
Styling